♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 28=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 28 =
Why did you ask Yun Xiangxiang to pretend as the daughter of Yun Group?
لماذا طلبت من يون شيانغشيانغ أن يتظاهر بأنه ابنة مجموعة يون؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Don't play dumb with me.
لا تلعب الغبي معي.
Regarding why she stays with you,
بخصوص سبب بقائها معك ،
you know it best.
أنت تعرفه أفضل.
Mr. Chu.
السيد.  تشو.
Don't you think
لا تعتقد
you are like a kid
انت مثل طفل
who can't get his favorite toy?
من لا يستطيع الحصول على لعبته المفضلة؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
I like her no matter she likes me or not.
أنا أحبها مهما كانت تحبني أم لا.
You came back in such a hurry
لقد عدت على عجل
because you were worried about this, right?
لأنك كنت قلقة بشأن هذا ، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Fu.
السيد فو.
I can stand up to protect her at any time.
يمكنني الوقوف لحمايتها في أي وقت.
Can you?
هل تستطيع؟
Stop.
قف.
Wait.
انتظر.
Leave the headwear.
اترك غطاء الرأس.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
Don't be mad at me.
لا تغضب مني.
Fu Sihan.
فو سيهان.
How could you just leave me there?
كيف يمكنك أن تتركني هناك؟
Humph!
همف!
Sorry.
آسف.
I just don't want to see him with you.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أراه معك.
You took it back?
هل استعادتها؟
Because
لان
this
هذه
is a couple.
هو زوجان.
Tsk.
تسك.
Childish.
طفولي.
Fu Sihan.
فو سيهان.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
لقد كنت أفكر في ذلك لفترة من الوقت.
And I decided to bring it up.
وقررت طرحه.
I think
أظن
the relationship contract
عقد العلاقة
is a bit inappropriate
قليلا غير مناسب
for us
لنا
now.
حاليا.
What did he tell you?
ماذا اخبرك؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Then why did you bring this up?
إذن لماذا طرحت هذا؟
Because
لان
why would a real couple
لماذا زوجين حقيقيين
need a relationship contract?
بحاجة الى عقد علاقة؟
Okay.
تمام.
Our contract
عقدنا
is terminated.
يتم إنهاء.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you are my real fiancee.
أنت خطيبتي الحقيقية.
Now...
حاليا...
It's a bit too soon.
إنه قريب جدًا.
For now,
الى الان،
you are just an intern boyfriend.
أنت مجرد صديقها المتدرب.
It depends on your performance
هذا يعتمد على أدائك
to become the official boyfriend.
ليصبح صديقها الرسمي.
Yeah.
نعم.
Fu Sihan!
فو سيهان!
You are cheating!
انت تغش!
So...
لذا...
Let's sleep
هيا ننام
now!
حاليا!
Okay.
تمام.
I'll watch you fall asleep.
سوف أشاهدك تنام.
No.
رقم.
I can't fall asleep if you are watching me.
لا أستطيع النوم إذا كنت تراقبني.
Then I'll keep my eyes closed.
ثم سأبقي عيني مغلقة.
Yeah.
نعم.
I'm asleep.
أنا نائم.
Okay.
تمام.
Why are you up so early?
لماذا انت مستيقظ باكرا؟
Why are there dark circles under your eyes?
لماذا هناك دوائر سوداء تحت عينيك؟
I stayed up.
بقيت مستيقظة.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I...
أنا...
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
You won't understand anyway.
لن تفهم على أي حال.
I'll sleep in my own room
سوف أنام في غرفتي الخاصة
tonight.
هذه الليلة.
Xiangxiang, look who's with us.
شيانغشيانغ ، انظر من معنا.
Xiangxiang, your auntie and cousin came to visit me.
Xiangxiang ، عمتك وابن عمك جاءوا لزيارتي.
Hello, Xiangxiang.
مرحبا Xiangxiang.
I haven't seen you for ages.
أنا لم أرك منذ زمن طويل.
You have to treat me with dinner today.
يجب أن تعاملني بالعشاء اليوم.
Why did they come?
لماذا جاءوا؟